[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "You're not that crazy guy anymore?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "that", "crazy", "guy", "anymore", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "No, I'm not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "Thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["Thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "I've got to say, you look great.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "got", "to", "say", ",", "you", "look", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "What do you feel about what you just watched there, yourself?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "what", "you", "just", "watched", "there", ",", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "EX", ",", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "It's a little cringeable.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "little", "cringeable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "Has your view of addiction and how to deal with it changed in -- in the two years since then?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "your", "view", "of", "addiction", "and", "how", "to", "deal", "with", "it", "changed", "in", "--", "in", "the", "two", "years", "since", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "It's softened a little bit.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "softened", "a", "little", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "You're not -- you're not that crazy guy anymore?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "--", "you", "'re", "not", "that", "crazy", "guy", "anymore", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "No, I'm not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "You could have avoided being fired, probably.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "could", "have", "avoided", "being", "fired", ",", "probably", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "How hard was it for you, even with all the experience you had, to have your life in this huge goldfish bowl over that period, where everybody was talking about nothing else but Charlie Sheen?", "question_tokens": ["How", "hard", "was", "it", "for", "you", ",", "even", "with", "all", "the", "experience", "you", "had", ",", "to", "have", "your", "life", "in", "this", "huge", "goldfish", "bowl", "over", "that", "period", ",", "where", "everybody", "was", "talking", "about", "nothing", "else", "but", "Charlie", "Sheen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "RB", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "It was -- it was pretty adrenal.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "--", "it", "was", "pretty", "adrenal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "I hadn't started yet?", "question_tokens": ["I", "had", "n't", "started", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "On the gun thing?", "question_tokens": ["On", "the", "gun", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "Yes, the stand you're taking is really -- it's really impressive.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "the", "stand", "you", "'re", "taking", "is", "really", "--", "it", "'s", "really", "impressive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2011"], "LOCATION": ["England", "Wales"]}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "How many -- how many homicides in your country last year with handguns?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "--", "how", "many", "homicides", "in", "your", "country", "last", "year", "with", "handguns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "Well, the last recorded year of 2011 in England and Wales was 39.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "last", "recorded", "year", "of", "2011", "in", "England", "and", "Wales", "was", "39", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", ":", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "Do you understand?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "understand", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "I think the problem that the people face -- well, there's two things.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "problem", "that", "the", "people", "face", "--", "well", ",", "there", "'s", "two", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "We have a standing army and all that, you know?", "question_tokens": ["We", "have", "a", "standing", "army", "and", "all", "that", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "-- I get why Americans want to defend themselves at home.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "I", "get", "why", "Americans", "want", "to", "defend", "themselves", "at", "home", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "Have you ever owned guns yourself?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "owned", "guns", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "I have, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "And how do you feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "I'm OK with it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "OK", "with", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "But do you -- do you miss having guns around?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "--", "do", "you", "miss", "having", "guns", "around", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "I miss shooting.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "miss", "shooting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 258, "question": "But I -- but I didn't -- I didn't carry and I didn't -- I didn't feel like, something that was a -- they were tools for -- for what I was using them for, not for all the negative stuff, you know?", "question_tokens": ["But", "I", "--", "but", "I", "did", "n't", "--", "I", "did", "n't", "carry", "and", "I", "did", "n't", "--", "I", "did", "n't", "feel", "like", ",", "something", "that", "was", "a", "--", "they", "were", "tools", "for", "--", "for", "what", "I", "was", "using", "them", "for", ",", "not", "for", "all", "the", "negative", "stuff", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", ":", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "When you see people say that, look, you can't ignore the influence of a violent Hollywood film --", "answer_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "people", "say", "that", ",", "look", ",", "you", "ca", "n't", "ignore", "the", "influence", "of", "a", "violent", "Hollywood", "film", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "-- influence people?", "question_tokens": ["--", "influence", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "Yes, I think it can.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "think", "it", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Quentin Tarantino"]}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "I think there's -- there's -- I think more damage can be done with a -- with a show like \"Criminal Minds,\" where like some guy is out there planning his next big serial kill and gets the idea from some of that stuff, where it's just really twisted and evil and hard to what watch, you know?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "'s", "--", "there", "'s", "--", "I", "think", "more", "damage", "can", "be", "done", "with", "a", "--", "with", "a", "show", "like", "``", "Criminal", "Minds", ",", "''", "where", "like", "some", "guy", "is", "out", "there", "planning", "his", "next", "big", "serial", "kill", "and", "gets", "the", "idea", "from", "some", "of", "that", "stuff", ",", "where", "it", "'s", "just", "really", "twisted", "and", "evil", "and", "hard", "to", "what", "watch", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", ":", "EX", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "``", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "''", "WRB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "TO", "WP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "I mean, Quentin Tarantino would argue, as he has done about his own films, that he merely reflects what is actually happening in real life.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "Quentin", "Tarantino", "would", "argue", ",", "as", "he", "has", "done", "about", "his", "own", "films", ",", "that", "he", "merely", "reflects", "what", "is", "actually", "happening", "in", "real", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "I don't know, I wish -- I wish I had a solution and I -- and I do, and I'm sure you feel the same way, you know?", "question_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "I", "wish", "--", "I", "wish", "I", "had", "a", "solution", "and", "I", "--", "and", "I", "do", ",", "and", "I", "'m", "sure", "you", "feel", "the", "same", "way", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "I feel very sort of frustrated, like I think a lot of people do, that you can't even have the debate.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "very", "sort", "of", "frustrated", ",", "like", "I", "think", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "do", ",", "that", "you", "ca", "n't", "even", "have", "the", "debate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "Which is why does anyone need an AR-15 military-style weapon anyway?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "is", "why", "does", "anyone", "need", "an", "AR-15", "military-style", "weapon", "anyway", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "WRB", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "Huh?", "question_tokens": ["Huh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "Fighting a war.", "answer_tokens": ["Fighting", "a", "war", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "What's your view of him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "view", "of", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "I met him once at a party and I'm assuming he was in a bad mood, because he wasn't the friendliest guy in the world.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "met", "him", "once", "at", "a", "party", "and", "I", "'m", "assuming", "he", "was", "in", "a", "bad", "mood", ",", "because", "he", "was", "n't", "the", "friendliest", "guy", "in", "the", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "He was rude to you?", "question_tokens": ["He", "was", "rude", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "Yes, I'm sure people have said that about me from time to time.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "'m", "sure", "people", "have", "said", "that", "about", "me", "from", "time", "to", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Armstrong"]}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "What did he say to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "he", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "I said, I said, Mr. Armstrong, I'm sorry to bother you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "said", ",", "I", "said", ",", "Mr.", "Armstrong", ",", "I", "'m", "sorry", "to", "bother", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "When was this?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "That's nice.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "nice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "When was this?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "And I said no, it's not nice, ass.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "I", "said", "no", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "nice", ",", "ass", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "And that's all he said to you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "that", "'s", "all", "he", "said", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Did he ever shake your hand?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "ever", "shake", "your", "hand", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "And then what happened?", "question_tokens": ["And", "then", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Again, I don't want to -- I don't want to, you know, tell both sides of the story, because I don't know what he was into that night, or what was going on.", "answer_tokens": ["Again", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", ",", "you", "know", ",", "tell", "both", "sides", "of", "the", "story", ",", "because", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "he", "was", "into", "that", "night", ",", "or", "what", "was", "going", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "CC", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "And then I just -- I -- I've just been on the sidelines with the rest of us watching the fall from grace, you know?", "question_tokens": ["And", "then", "I", "just", "--", "I", "--", "I", "'ve", "just", "been", "on", "the", "sidelines", "with", "the", "rest", "of", "us", "watching", "the", "fall", "from", "grace", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "I mean, to me, he's one of the biggest and worst cheats in sporting history, because the number of lives that he adversely affected -- you know, I get all the Livestrong thing.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "to", "me", ",", "he", "'s", "one", "of", "the", "biggest", "and", "worst", "cheats", "in", "sporting", "history", ",", "because", "the", "number", "of", "lives", "that", "he", "adversely", "affected", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "get", "all", "the", "Livestrong", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lance"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "I think America is very forgiving if the person hasn't been like you described some of the behavior that that Lance pursued.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "America", "is", "very", "forgiving", "if", "the", "person", "has", "n't", "been", "like", "you", "described", "some", "of", "the", "behavior", "that", "that", "Lance", "pursued", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "JJ", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Which film was that?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "film", "was", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "\"Major League.\"", "answer_tokens": ["``", "Major", "League", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "Did it really?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "it", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "It made me crazy.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "made", "me", "crazy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 363, "question": "A lot of people talk about Bonds and well, you know, this Hall of Fame thing recently that I think was kind of a bit of a disaster, you know?", "question_tokens": ["A", "lot", "of", "people", "talk", "about", "Bonds", "and", "well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "this", "Hall", "of", "Fame", "thing", "recently", "that", "I", "think", "was", "kind", "of", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "disaster", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Well, it was a disaster --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "a", "disaster", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hall"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "So, I mean, why would you put a cheat into the Hall of Fame?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "why", "would", "you", "put", "a", "cheat", "into", "the", "Hall", "of", "Fame", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Well, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hall"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Monday"], "TIME": ["morning"]}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "Do you forgive Lance Armstrong then?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "forgive", "Lance", "Armstrong", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "HEEN: I'd like to sit down and talk to him and make my own opinion based on an experience with him, not just based on, you know, sideline Monday morning quarterbacking.", "answer_tokens": ["HEEN", ":", "I", "'d", "like", "to", "sit", "down", "and", "talk", "to", "him", "and", "make", "my", "own", "opinion", "based", "on", "an", "experience", "with", "him", ",", "not", "just", "based", "on", ",", "you", "know", ",", "sideline", "Monday", "morning", "quarterbacking", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lance Armstrong"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "What's a man cave?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "a", "man", "cave", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "It's a place where you can do whatever you want and nobody bothers you.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "place", "where", "you", "can", "do", "whatever", "you", "want", "and", "nobody", "bothers", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ":", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Does it ever get easier?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "ever", "get", "easier", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Life imitating -- yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Life", "imitating", "--", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 444, "question": "Because I have \"Charlie Swan\" coming out also, you know?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "I", "have", "``", "Charlie", "Swan", "''", "coming", "out", "also", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBG", "RP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "I know you did a new movie --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "you", "did", "a", "new", "movie", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "You're giving up Charlie completely?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "giving", "up", "Charlie", "completely", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"]}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "In all -- in all senses?", "question_tokens": ["In", "all", "--", "in", "all", "senses", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "HEEN: -- I didn't have any children, Charlie.", "answer_tokens": ["HEEN", ":", "--", "I", "did", "n't", "have", "any", "children", ",", "Charlie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "I think over 90, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "over", "90", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "Is it more fun doing these sort of shows sober?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "more", "fun", "doing", "these", "sort", "of", "shows", "sober", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "It's a lot more fun, yes, because you can make a lot more choices.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "lot", "more", "fun", ",", "yes", ",", "because", "you", "can", "make", "a", "lot", "more", "choices", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "Do you -- do you still party much or?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "--", "do", "you", "still", "party", "much", "or", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "CC", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "Not as much as I used to.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "as", "much", "as", "I", "used", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "You haven't completely given up?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "n't", "completely", "given", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "But, and I think that -- that can slow down the choices that -- that one can make, you know?", "question_tokens": ["But", ",", "and", "I", "think", "that", "--", "that", "can", "slow", "down", "the", "choices", "that", "--", "that", "one", "can", "make", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "IN", "MD", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", ":", "IN", "CD", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "ORGAN: But does that really -- I've always wondered if that really makes a difference.", "answer_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "But", "does", "that", "really", "--", "I", "'ve", "always", "wondered", "if", "that", "really", "makes", "a", "difference", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["AA Nazis"]}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "WRB", "DT", ":", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 524, "question": "If you're playing a womanizing party boy, why would looking hangover be brand damaging?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "'re", "playing", "a", "womanizing", "party", "boy", ",", "why", "would", "looking", "hangover", "be", "brand", "damaging", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "VBG", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "It shouldn't be, but when the -- when the show is run by AA Nazis, then it takes on a different light --", "answer_tokens": ["It", "should", "n't", "be", ",", "but", "when", "the", "--", "when", "the", "show", "is", "run", "by", "AA", "Nazis", ",", "then", "it", "takes", "on", "a", "different", "light", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "So come on, how -- how do you get on with him these days?", "question_tokens": ["So", "come", "on", ",", "how", "--", "how", "do", "you", "get", "on", "with", "him", "these", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBN", "IN", ",", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "I still haven't spoken to him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "still", "have", "n't", "spoken", "to", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "Not a single word?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "a", "single", "word", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "No, nothing, zero, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "nothing", ",", "zero", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "What would you have said if you had bumped into him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "have", "said", "if", "you", "had", "bumped", "into", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "I'd have walked right up to him and said, hey, man, you know, good luck with everything.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "have", "walked", "right", "up", "to", "him", "and", "said", ",", "hey", ",", "man", ",", "you", "know", ",", "good", "luck", "with", "everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "Do you harbor resentments toward him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "harbor", "resentments", "toward", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "I get -- yes, I just wish that -- that he would acknowledge, at some point, that he had a hand in it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "get", "--", "yes", ",", "I", "just", "wish", "that", "--", "that", "he", "would", "acknowledge", ",", "at", "some", "point", ",", "that", "he", "had", "a", "hand", "in", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NNS", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "``", "CD", "CC", "DT", "NNP", ",", "''", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "-- do you miss him?", "question_tokens": ["--", "do", "you", "miss", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "There's parts of him I miss -- yes, because when I look back at the -- at the -- at the pilot of \"Two and A Half,\" it was an absolute gem.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "parts", "of", "him", "I", "miss", "--", "yes", ",", "because", "when", "I", "look", "back", "at", "the", "--", "at", "the", "--", "at", "the", "pilot", "of", "``", "Two", "and", "A", "Half", ",", "''", "it", "was", "an", "absolute", "gem", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "Would you?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "Just for the record, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "for", "the", "record", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "Is this show good with him, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "show", "good", "with", "him", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "Do you ever watch it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "watch", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "I watched it early on.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "watched", "it", "early", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "Do you ever speak to him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "speak", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "Was he friendly to you?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "friendly", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "No, he was -- he was fabulous, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "was", "--", "he", "was", "fabulous", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "IN", "``", "CD", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 634, "question": "Are you all completely crack heads (ph) on this show?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "all", "completely", "crack", "heads", "(", "ph", ")", "on", "this", "show", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "Angus, what does the Bible say about \"Two and A Half Men?\"", "answer_tokens": ["Angus", ",", "what", "does", "the", "Bible", "say", "about", "``", "Two", "and", "A", "Half", "Men", "?", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "Well, when you -- when you first saw that, what did you think?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "when", "you", "--", "when", "you", "first", "saw", "that", ",", "what", "did", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "I didn't think it was an act.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "think", "it", "was", "an", "act", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 645, "question": "Had he shown any signs of this kind of extreme religious philosophy or?", "question_tokens": ["Had", "he", "shown", "any", "signs", "of", "this", "kind", "of", "extreme", "religious", "philosophy", "or", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "."], "aSentId": 646, "answer": "Not even close.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "even", "close", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "It was never -- religion was never -- I think there was one episode about it, but, you know, it wasn't like a water cooler topic or anything, you know?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", "never", "--", "religion", "was", "never", "--", "I", "think", "there", "was", "one", "episode", "about", "it", ",", "but", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "was", "n't", "like", "a", "water", "cooler", "topic", "or", "anything", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "NN", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "But when he went off like this, he then regretted it and said he wished he hadn't.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "when", "he", "went", "off", "like", "this", ",", "he", "then", "regretted", "it", "and", "said", "he", "wished", "he", "had", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "You know what I'm saying?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", "I", "'m", "saying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "So, Charlie, why did you give Lindsay Lohan $100,000?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "Charlie", ",", "why", "did", "you", "give", "Lindsay", "Lohan", "$", "100,000", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "$", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "Good question.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$100,000"], "PERSON": ["Charlie", "Lindsay Lohan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 678, "question": "Did you get it back?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "get", "it", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 679, "answer": "No, no, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 692, "question": "Was she grateful?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "she", "grateful", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 693, "answer": "Eventually.", "answer_tokens": ["Eventually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 695, "question": "Eventually?", "question_tokens": ["Eventually", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 696, "answer": "Eventually, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Eventually", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 700, "question": "She's a busy young lady, you know?", "question_tokens": ["She", "'s", "a", "busy", "young", "lady", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 701, "answer": "She is, in many ways, someone who has gone through a not dissimilar path from you.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "is", ",", "in", "many", "ways", ",", "someone", "who", "has", "gone", "through", "a", "not", "dissimilar", "path", "from", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "Or is it, in the end, the look in the mirror and work it out for yourself?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "it", ",", "in", "the", "end", ",", "the", "look", "in", "the", "mirror", "and", "work", "it", "out", "for", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "If -- the only thing that I was sad about -- if she had asked me questions about some of my own stuff, I would have gladly given her advice, but she didn't.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "--", "the", "only", "thing", "that", "I", "was", "sad", "about", "--", "if", "she", "had", "asked", "me", "questions", "about", "some", "of", "my", "own", "stuff", ",", "I", "would", "have", "gladly", "given", "her", "advice", ",", "but", "she", "did", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 736, "question": "When you react in the way that you do, which was pretty aggressively against what he said, how did he respond to that?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "react", "in", "the", "way", "that", "you", "do", ",", "which", "was", "pretty", "aggressively", "against", "what", "he", "said", ",", "how", "did", "he", "respond", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 737, "answer": "He didn't.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "did", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 741, "question": "And did that happen?", "question_tokens": ["And", "did", "that", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "Oh, hell yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "hell", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 743, "question": "How did that happen?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "that", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 744, "answer": "There was a moment we had where -- I think the tour ended.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "was", "a", "moment", "we", "had", "where", "--", "I", "think", "the", "tour", "ended", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 760, "question": "You speak to him much now?", "question_tokens": ["You", "speak", "to", "him", "much", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 761, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 768, "question": "Does he know how possibly influential he's been on your recovery?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "know", "how", "possibly", "influential", "he", "'s", "been", "on", "your", "recovery", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 769, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 771, "question": "Which must makes him very proud?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "must", "makes", "him", "very", "proud", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "MD", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 772, "answer": "It does It does.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "It", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 780, "question": "Or is everyone different?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "everyone", "different", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 781, "answer": "They handle it differently.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "handle", "it", "differently", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 808, "question": "You're like, now what?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "like", ",", "now", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "RB", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 809, "answer": "But it may save your life.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "it", "may", "save", "your", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 815, "question": "Is that always the demon on your shoulder?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "always", "the", "demon", "on", "your", "shoulder", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 816, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 822, "question": "I think it just -- again, things just sort of got ahead of themselves and you start playing catch-up, trying to put the blocks back together, you know?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "just", "--", "again", ",", "things", "just", "sort", "of", "got", "ahead", "of", "themselves", "and", "you", "start", "playing", "catch-up", ",", "trying", "to", "put", "the", "blocks", "back", "together", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ":", "RB", ",", "NNS", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 823, "answer": "Because I thought a lot of it was very entertaining, if I'm honest with you.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "thought", "a", "lot", "of", "it", "was", "very", "entertaining", ",", "if", "I", "'m", "honest", "with", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Detroit"]}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 837, "question": "Did you have a moment where you suddenly went, I'm not doing this anymore, or certainly not at the level I have been doing it?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "a", "moment", "where", "you", "suddenly", "went", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "doing", "this", "anymore", ",", "or", "certainly", "not", "at", "the", "level", "I", "have", "been", "doing", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 838, "answer": "It was in Detroit, opening night.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "in", "Detroit", ",", "opening", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["two years ago"], "PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 852, "question": "And I did, against all odds, you know?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "did", ",", "against", "all", "odds", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 853, "answer": "I look at you now and I see somebody not unrecognizable from two years ago, but certainly a very different Charlie Sheen.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "look", "at", "you", "now", "and", "I", "see", "somebody", "not", "unrecognizable", "from", "two", "years", "ago", ",", "but", "certainly", "a", "very", "different", "Charlie", "Sheen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "TO", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 865, "question": "Not bad, right?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "bad", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 866, "answer": "Perfect link to what the next segment --", "answer_tokens": ["Perfect", "link", "to", "what", "the", "next", "segment", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 867, "question": "Is it about horses?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "about", "horses", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 868, "answer": "It's about women.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "about", "women", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 890, "question": "You enjoyed making it?", "question_tokens": ["You", "enjoyed", "making", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 891, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 895, "question": "Where are you at the moment with women?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "you", "at", "the", "moment", "with", "women", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 896, "answer": "With a girlfriend.", "answer_tokens": ["With", "a", "girlfriend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 897, "question": "A goddess?", "question_tokens": ["A", "goddess", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 898, "answer": "No, just a girlfriend.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "just", "a", "girlfriend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 899, "question": "What happened to the goddesses?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happened", "to", "the", "goddesses", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 900, "answer": "They went their separate ways.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "went", "their", "separate", "ways", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 903, "question": "Every man's dream or does it get complicated?", "question_tokens": ["Every", "man", "'s", "dream", "or", "does", "it", "get", "complicated", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 904, "answer": "It gets complicated, yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "gets", "complicated", ",", "yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 916, "question": "She's an adult entertainer?", "question_tokens": ["She", "'s", "an", "adult", "entertainer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 917, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 932, "question": "She's given it up?", "question_tokens": ["She", "'s", "given", "it", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 933, "answer": "Yes, a couple years.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "a", "couple", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 938, "question": "Are you in love with her?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "in", "love", "with", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 939, "answer": "Yes, I am.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 945, "question": "Were you properly in love each time?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "properly", "in", "love", "each", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 946, "answer": "I thought I was.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "I", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 962, "question": "ORGAN: She's now in her late 20s, your daughter, right?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "She", "'s", "now", "in", "her", "late", "20s", ",", "your", "daughter", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "CD", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 963, "answer": "She's 28.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "28", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 978, "question": "And how are your kids, your twin boys?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "are", "your", "kids", ",", "your", "twin", "boys", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 979, "answer": "They're pretty good.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "pretty", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 986, "question": "Do you see much of the boys?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "see", "much", "of", "the", "boys", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 987, "answer": "Sorry.", "answer_tokens": ["Sorry", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 992, "question": "How many kids?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "kids", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 993, "answer": "I have five.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "five", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 996, "question": "Are they all friends with each other, the kids?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "all", "friends", "with", "each", "other", ",", "the", "kids", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 997, "answer": "They're becoming friends, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "becoming", "friends", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 999, "question": "When you see the influence and impact your father had on you, do you understand more of the power of you as a father to be a role model to you kids?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "the", "influence", "and", "impact", "your", "father", "had", "on", "you", ",", "do", "you", "understand", "more", "of", "the", "power", "of", "you", "as", "a", "father", "to", "be", "a", "role", "model", "to", "you", "kids", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 1000, "answer": "To a degree, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "a", "degree", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1001, "question": "Are you ready for that?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "ready", "for", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 1002, "answer": "I believe that I am, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "believe", "that", "I", "am", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1005, "question": "What would be the number one bit of advice you give one of your sons, perhaps?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "be", "the", "number", "one", "bit", "of", "advice", "you", "give", "one", "of", "your", "sons", ",", "perhaps", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 1006, "answer": "Live with the truth.", "answer_tokens": ["Live", "with", "the", "truth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1063, "question": "How would you go on if he brought that particular style to the Oscars?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "go", "on", "if", "he", "brought", "that", "particular", "style", "to", "the", "Oscars", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1064, "answer": "He might want to tone it down just a little bit.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "might", "want", "to", "tone", "it", "down", "just", "a", "little", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 1071, "question": "He was great at the roast, wasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "was", "great", "at", "the", "roast", ",", "was", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1072, "answer": "He was superb.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "superb", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 1090, "question": "I thought it was pretty good, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "thought", "it", "was", "pretty", "good", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 1091, "answer": "It was fantastic.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "fantastic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 1093, "question": "Did any of it hurt you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "any", "of", "it", "hurt", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1094, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 1101, "question": "Have you seen many movies?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "seen", "many", "movies", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 1102, "answer": "Not too many.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "too", "many", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Atlanta"]}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBD", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 1103, "question": "Do you ever actually go and buy a ticket and go to a movie theater?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "actually", "go", "and", "buy", "a", "ticket", "and", "go", "to", "a", "movie", "theater", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1104, "answer": "When I was in Atlanta, I went and saw \"Safe House\" a few months ago.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "I", "was", "in", "Atlanta", ",", "I", "went", "and", "saw", "``", "Safe", "House", "''", "a", "few", "months", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 1110, "question": "How do they react?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "they", "react", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 1111, "answer": "HEEN: They usually wait until the film is over to talk to me, which is polite.", "answer_tokens": ["HEEN", ":", "They", "usually", "wait", "until", "the", "film", "is", "over", "to", "talk", "to", "me", ",", "which", "is", "polite", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1113, "question": "Are you, at your heart, a movie star, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", ",", "at", "your", "heart", ",", "a", "movie", "star", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 1114, "answer": "I'm a baseball player in my heart.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "baseball", "player", "in", "my", "heart", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 1119, "question": "That would have been the dream for you?", "question_tokens": ["That", "would", "have", "been", "the", "dream", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1120, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 1127, "question": "Would you really?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 1128, "answer": "Absolutely, at the drop of a hat.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", ",", "at", "the", "drop", "of", "a", "hat", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "``", "JJ", "NNP", "''", "CC", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 1137, "question": "Why is he so good?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "he", "so", "good", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 1138, "answer": "Because he did \"Fast Times\" and \"Dead Men Walking.\"", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "he", "did", "``", "Fast", "Times", "''", "and", "``", "Dead", "Men", "Walking", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 1147, "question": "ORGAN: Who is the best actress?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Who", "is", "the", "best", "actress", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1148, "answer": "Wow.", "answer_tokens": ["Wow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 1150, "question": "You'd have to almost -- you'd have to go with Streep I think, you know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'d", "have", "to", "almost", "--", "you", "'d", "have", "to", "go", "with", "Streep", "I", "think", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 1151, "answer": "Just for sheer amount of amazing --", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "for", "sheer", "amount", "of", "amazing", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 1158, "question": "Will you be watching the Oscars?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "you", "be", "watching", "the", "Oscars", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1159, "answer": "I will, indeed.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "will", ",", "indeed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 1169, "question": "Daniel Day-Lewis?", "question_tokens": ["Daniel", "Day-Lewis", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1170, "answer": "Yes, he's number two.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "he", "'s", "number", "two", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Daniel Day-Lewis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 1174, "question": "Are you still winning, Charlie?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "still", "winning", ",", "Charlie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1175, "answer": "Today I am with you.", "answer_tokens": ["Today", "I", "am", "with", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"]}}]